<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>minor-pantheon on</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/tags/minor-pantheon/</link><description>Recent content in minor-pantheon on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/tags/minor-pantheon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aegir</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Aegir/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Aegir/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral-Evil Goddess of the sea and storms Death, Nature, Tempest A twisting maelstrom The Wrath of the Sea (she/her) Description Aegir’s temples are openly fortified against the works of mortals and against the elements of nature.</description></item><item><title>Forseti</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Forseti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Forseti/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral God of justice, peacemaker Arcana, Knowledge, Order, Protection A bearded man with covered eyes, blind The Peacemaker (he/him) Description Forseti, son of Balder, has never told a lie.</description></item><item><title>Heimdall</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Heimdall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Heimdall/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Good God of watchfulness and loyalty Knowledge, Light, Order, War A curved battle horn The All-Seeing (he/him) Description Heimdall is the gatekeeper and guardian of the Bifrost, the rainbow bridge that connects Asgard and Midgard.</description></item><item><title>Hermod</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Hermod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Hermod/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Neutral God of luck Arcana, Knowledge, Trickery A coin flipping through the air The Lucky (they/them) Description Hermod, the messenger god, is another god of luck and trickery.</description></item><item><title>Njord</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Njord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Njord/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral-Good God of sea and wind Nature, Tempest, War An old man with a worn traveler’s cloak taking shelter from a storm The Restless (he/him) Description Once the husband of Skadi, since his marriage ended Njord has mostly withdrawn to Asgard.</description></item><item><title>Sif</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Sif/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Sif/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Good Goddess of heritage, protection, honor Protection, Strength, War An upraised sword wrapped in fire The Honor-Bound (she/her) Description Wife to Thor and mother to Uller, Sif the Honor-Bound is a fierce golden-haired goddess of battle.</description></item><item><title>Thrym</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Thrym/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Thrym/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Evil God of frost giants and cold Death, Nature, Tempest, War White double-bladed axe coated in frost The King of Frost (he/him) Description Thrym makes his home in the Frozen North of Jotunheim.</description></item><item><title>Uller</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Uller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Uller/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Neutral Goddess of hunting and winter Life, Nature A drawn longbow knocked with an arrow The Huntress (she/her) Description Uller, goddess of archery and the hunt, is Thor’s only daughter.</description></item></channel></rss>