<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gods on</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/gods/</link><description>Recent content in Gods on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/gods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aegir</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Aegir/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Aegir/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral-Evil Goddess of the sea and storms Death, Nature, Tempest A twisting maelstrom The Wrath of the Sea (she/her) Description Aegir’s temples are openly fortified against the works of mortals and against the elements of nature.</description></item><item><title>Balder</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Balder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Balder/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral-Good Beauty, poetry and literature, artists and scholars, flora and fauna Arcana, Knowledge, Life, Light, Peace, Nature Wreath of grass and grain affixed to a crook The Artist’s Heart (he/him) Description The son of Odin, Balder is the god of beauty, art, and poetry.</description></item><item><title>Divinity in Viken</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Divinity-in-Viken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Divinity-in-Viken/</guid><description>[[Viken]]’s people have been steeped in war, conflict, and struggles for survival since the continent’s founding. Divinity is very important to the people of [[Viken]].</description></item><item><title>Forseti</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Forseti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Forseti/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral God of justice, peacemaker Arcana, Knowledge, Order, Protection A bearded man with covered eyes, blind The Peacemaker (he/him) Description Forseti, son of Balder, has never told a lie.</description></item><item><title>Freya</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Freya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Freya/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral-Good Life, the Sun, fertility, healing, family, motherhood Life, Light, Nature, Peace A falcon taking flight The Loving Mother (she/her) Description Freya’s domain is the Sun, life itself, motherhood and fertility.</description></item><item><title>Gods</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Gods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Gods/</guid><description>%% Zoottelkeeper: Beginning of the autogenerated index file list %%
[[content/Gods/Aegir|Aegir]] [[content/Gods/Balder|Balder]] [[content/Gods/Divinity in Viken|Divinity in Viken]] [[content/Gods/Forseti|Forseti]] [[content/Gods/Freya|Freya]] [[content/Gods/Heimdall|Heimdall]] [[content/Gods/Hel|Hel]] [[content/Gods/Hermod|Hermod]] [[content/Gods/Loki|Loki]] [[content/Gods/Njord|Njord]] [[content/Gods/Odin|Odin]] [[content/Gods/Sif|Sif]] [[content/Gods/Skadi|Skadi]] [[content/Gods/Surtur|Surtur]] [[content/Gods/Thor|Thor]] [[content/Gods/Thrym|Thrym]] [[content/Gods/Uller|Uller]] %% Zoottelkeeper: End of the autogenerated index file list %%</description></item><item><title>Heimdall</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Heimdall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Heimdall/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Good God of watchfulness and loyalty Knowledge, Light, Order, War A curved battle horn The All-Seeing (he/him) Description Heimdall is the gatekeeper and guardian of the Bifrost, the rainbow bridge that connects Asgard and Midgard.</description></item><item><title>Hel</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Hel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Hel/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral Death and the afterlife, the underworld, twilight, the moon Grave, Death, Twilight A silhouette of a cloaked woman, wreathed in tendrils of shadow Goddess of the Underworld (she/her) Description Master of the skein of fate and the mistress of winter, Hel is the god of death.</description></item><item><title>Hermod</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Hermod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Hermod/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Neutral God of luck Arcana, Knowledge, Trickery A coin flipping through the air The Lucky (they/them) Description Hermod, the messenger god, is another god of luck and trickery.</description></item><item><title>Loki</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Loki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Loki/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Evil Trickery, thieves, wittiness Knowledge, Trickery A grinning white mask topped with curved horns The Trickster God (he/him/she/her/they/them) Description Loki was not always an Aesir.</description></item><item><title>Njord</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Njord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Njord/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral-Good God of sea and wind Nature, Tempest, War An old man with a worn traveler’s cloak taking shelter from a storm The Restless (he/him) Description Once the husband of Skadi, since his marriage ended Njord has mostly withdrawn to Asgard.</description></item><item><title>Odin</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Odin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Odin/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Good Civilization, order, law, justice, and peace Knowledge, Order A simple axe inlaid with gold scales The All-Father Description At the top of the tallest building in the highest realm of Asgard, Odin, the All-Father of the world and the gods who inhabit it, sits atop his throne, the Lidskjalf.</description></item><item><title>Sif</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Sif/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Sif/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Good Goddess of heritage, protection, honor Protection, Strength, War An upraised sword wrapped in fire The Honor-Bound (she/her) Description Wife to Thor and mother to Uller, Sif the Honor-Bound is a fierce golden-haired goddess of battle.</description></item><item><title>Skadi</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Skadi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Skadi/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Neutral Earth and mountains, craftsmanship, beauty, the forge Forge, Knowledge, Nature, Order A gem-encrusted forging hammer Mother of the Forge (she/her) Description Skadi is a female giant whose father Sleipnir built the great walls protecting Asgard.</description></item><item><title>Surtur</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Surtur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Surtur/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Evil Fire giants and war, strength of arms, ends justify the means, exploitation Death, War A crown of wicked black thorns, dripping blood Lord of Fire (he/him) Description Surtur sits atop the Black Throne in the Wastes of Muspelheim as Master of Tyranny, Vengeance and Desolation.</description></item><item><title>Thor</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Thor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Thor/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Good Storms and thunder, courage, glory in battle, competition Strength, Tempest, Nature, War A hammer over crossed lightning bolts God of Storms and Thunder (he/him) Description Strongest of the Aesir is Odin’s son, Thor, the god of storms and thunder.</description></item><item><title>Thrym</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Thrym/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Thrym/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Evil God of frost giants and cold Death, Nature, Tempest, War White double-bladed axe coated in frost The King of Frost (he/him) Description Thrym makes his home in the Frozen North of Jotunheim.</description></item><item><title>Uller</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Uller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/viken-notes-obsidian/Gods/Uller/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Neutral Goddess of hunting and winter Life, Nature A drawn longbow knocked with an arrow The Huntress (she/her) Description Uller, goddess of archery and the hunt, is Thor’s only daughter.</description></item></channel></rss>