<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>major-pantheon on</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/tags/major-pantheon/</link><description>Recent content in major-pantheon on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://khreezy.github.io/tags/major-pantheon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Balder</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Balder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Balder/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral-Good Beauty, poetry and literature, artists and scholars, flora and fauna Arcana, Knowledge, Life, Light, Peace, Nature Wreath of grass and grain affixed to a crook The Artist’s Heart (he/him) Description The son of Odin, Balder is the god of beauty, art, and poetry.</description></item><item><title>Hel</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Hel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Hel/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Neutral Death and the afterlife, the underworld, twilight, the moon Grave, Death, Twilight A silhouette of a cloaked woman, wreathed in tendrils of shadow Goddess of the Underworld (she/her) Description Master of the skein of fate and the mistress of winter, Hel is the god of death.</description></item><item><title>Loki</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Loki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Loki/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Evil Trickery, thieves, wittiness Knowledge, Trickery A grinning white mask topped with curved horns The Trickster God (he/him/she/her/they/them) Description Loki was not always an Aesir.</description></item><item><title>Odin</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Odin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Odin/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Good Civilization, order, law, justice, and peace Knowledge, Order A simple axe inlaid with gold scales The All-Father Description At the top of the tallest building in the highest realm of Asgard, Odin, the All-Father of the world and the gods who inhabit it, sits atop his throne, the Lidskjalf.</description></item><item><title>Skadi</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Skadi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Skadi/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Neutral Earth and mountains, craftsmanship, beauty, the forge Forge, Knowledge, Nature, Order A gem-encrusted forging hammer Mother of the Forge (she/her) Description Skadi is a female giant whose father Sleipnir built the great walls protecting Asgard.</description></item><item><title>Surtur</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Surtur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Surtur/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Lawful-Evil Fire giants and war, strength of arms, ends justify the means, exploitation Death, War A crown of wicked black thorns, dripping blood Lord of Fire (he/him) Description Surtur sits atop the Black Throne in the Wastes of Muspelheim as Master of Tyranny, Vengeance and Desolation.</description></item><item><title>Thor</title><link>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Thor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khreezy.github.io/Gods/Thor/</guid><description>Alignment Province Suggested Domains Common Symbology Chaotic-Good Storms and thunder, courage, glory in battle, competition Strength, Tempest, Nature, War A hammer over crossed lightning bolts God of Storms and Thunder (he/him) Description Strongest of the Aesir is Odin’s son, Thor, the god of storms and thunder.</description></item></channel></rss>